{
    "id": "59bc97ac832d4ad68ac531aee8a64bc7",
    "title": "Direct And Indirect Speech Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The boy said that he ................. very busy then.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "has been",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "bfe57172296049b9a73e9ce4977b9494"
        },
        {
            "question": "The mother asked the girl where ........................ going?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "she was",
                "was she",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8c55f59156d44ee280243815262fc9b5"
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher asked the students if they ........................... their homework.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "had done",
                "did",
                "had done"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dbac1fc9c8724ae092235323bf0a985a"
        },
        {
            "question": "She said that she .......................... her job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "finished",
                "has finished",
                "had finished"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9e662ecc5f404b47806b9c63107a3350"
        },
        {
            "question": "He said that his father ........................... working in the garage.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was",
                "has been"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "aab4516c0f004e50ab71a2ac2602d03e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I said that I ......................... the examination.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have passed",
                "had passed",
                "was passed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "489c03b360424d62b32038d4be0eee57"
        },
        {
            "question": "The man said that the horse ........................ in the night.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "dies",
                "has died",
                "had died"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "654fff79520744c7a982d6c199003ec3"
        },
        {
            "question": "He told me that he ............................. me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "doesn't believe",
                "didn't believe",
                "don't believe"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "be4cbad68fed459e90556d18ff9debcd"
        },
        {
            "question": "I told him that I ....................... believe him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "don't",
                "didn't",
                "haven't"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2d723135fe2b44958604c47b18aacf06"
        },
        {
            "question": "He says that he .................... glad to be here in this evening.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "has been",
                "had been"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8bc065304b3844aeab348e4167db7859"
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher says that the earth ..................... round the sun.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "moves",
                "moved",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "67595520b8cb4cebb5b43ceb81729690"
        },
        {
            "question": "The report says that global temperatures ...................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are rising",
                "were rising",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3068c1ba621047c6a2754a5cf6146eac"
        }
    ]
}